[{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980248968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":12942,"timeElapsed":65814},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980255177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6206,"timeElapsed":72023},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980263359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":8181,"timeElapsed":80205},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980274084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":10723,"timeElapsed":90930},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980280013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":5927,"timeElapsed":96859},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980290736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":10721,"timeElapsed":107581},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980298852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8114,"timeElapsed":115697},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980307077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8224,"timeElapsed":123923},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980314809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7729,"timeElapsed":131654},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":5494,"timeElapsed":139789},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980327751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4806,"timeElapsed":144597},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980332183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":4431,"timeElapsed":149029},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980336489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4304,"timeElapsed":153335},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980341261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4771,"timeElapsed":158107},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":6297,"timeElapsed":164406},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980355622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":8060,"timeElapsed":172468},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980361005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5381,"timeElapsed":177851},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980366642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":5636,"timeElapsed":183488},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980380013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":11935,"timeElapsed":196859},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":6193,"timeElapsed":203054},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980390717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":4508,"timeElapsed":207563},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980397104,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":6385,"timeElapsed":213950},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980401738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4632,"timeElapsed":218584},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980407091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5352,"timeElapsed":223937},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":4751,"timeElapsed":228690},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":7169,"timeElapsed":235860},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980422436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3421,"timeElapsed":239282},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429311,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6873,"timeElapsed":246157},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6463,"timeElapsed":254243},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980441196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3797,"timeElapsed":258042},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4621,"timeElapsed":262664},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980451053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":5233,"timeElapsed":267898},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980455213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4159,"timeElapsed":272059},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980459806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4591,"timeElapsed":276652},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980466045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":6237,"timeElapsed":282891},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":5108,"timeElapsed":288000},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980478866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":7710,"timeElapsed":295712},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980494604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14307,"timeElapsed":311450},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4754,"timeElapsed":316206},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980502873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3512,"timeElapsed":319719},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980508090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5216,"timeElapsed":324936},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980512839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":4747,"timeElapsed":329685},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980517190,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":4350,"timeElapsed":334036},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980521945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4753,"timeElapsed":338791},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980529294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":7347,"timeElapsed":346140},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3856,"timeElapsed":349998},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6620,"timeElapsed":358263},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3130,"timeElapsed":361395},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980547786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3235,"timeElapsed":364632},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980551896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4108,"timeElapsed":368742},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980555052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3155,"timeElapsed":371898},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980561145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6091,"timeElapsed":377991},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4769,"timeElapsed":382761},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980571643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5726,"timeElapsed":388489},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3535,"timeElapsed":392025},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6747,"timeElapsed":400229},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980586559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3174,"timeElapsed":403405},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980589692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3131,"timeElapsed":406538},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":5196,"timeElapsed":411735},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980597415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2524,"timeElapsed":414261},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5874,"timeElapsed":420136},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980605707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2415,"timeElapsed":422553},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980611697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5989,"timeElapsed":428542},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980614595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2897,"timeElapsed":431441},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":8610,"timeElapsed":441498},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980630570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":5917,"timeElapsed":447416},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3040,"timeElapsed":450458},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980638215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4602,"timeElapsed":455061},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980640965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2750,"timeElapsed":457811},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980646010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5044,"timeElapsed":462856},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980649142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3131,"timeElapsed":465988},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5291,"timeElapsed":471281},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980658689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":4253,"timeElapsed":475535},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":5443,"timeElapsed":482235},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2604,"timeElapsed":484841},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2726,"timeElapsed":487568},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3570,"timeElapsed":491140},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980676846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2551,"timeElapsed":493692},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":5319,"timeElapsed":499012},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2928,"timeElapsed":501941},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5384,"timeElapsed":507327},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980695790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":5308,"timeElapsed":512636},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701546,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5755,"timeElapsed":518392},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980710003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":6996,"timeElapsed":526849},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2796,"timeElapsed":529647},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980716210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3408,"timeElapsed":533056},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980719637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3425,"timeElapsed":536483},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980722530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2891,"timeElapsed":539375},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4138,"timeElapsed":543516},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980728914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2243,"timeElapsed":545760},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980735922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7006,"timeElapsed":552768},{"subjectID":"apoc027z7j","prolificID":"654129680a8917e0f46a89aa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b228629b4e272d42e9f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4587,"timeElapsed":557356}]